LAODE GHAZY NAUFAL IKSYAM

082247086016 | 19523176@STUNDENTS.UII.AC.ID LOMBOK.NUSATENGGARABARAT

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a undergraduate semester student in the informatics study program at the Islamic University of Indonesia. Actively participate in organizations and events held on campus. I am enthusiastic, active, honest and responsible. In addition, I also have a great curiosity, dare to try new things, easily adapt to new environments and can work under pressure. I believe that joining your company will give me more experience to develop and improve my skills and knowledge.

EDUCATION

Indonesian Islamic University - Yogyakarta, INDONESIA | Aug 2019 - Now

Area of Interest: Front End Developer, UI/UX Design

GPA: 3.42

MAN 2 MATARAM | 2017-2019

Science Major

SKILLS

- Able to Operate Visual Studio Code
- Able to Operate Figma and Canva
- Able to Operate GitHub
- Able to Operate Google Suite, Jira, Trello
- Able to Operate Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Power Point)
- Proficient in ReactJS, HTML, CSS, Kotlin, C++, Javascript, C#

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer | Skill Academy By Ruang Guru - Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2022 – Jul 2022

• Participate in Front End Developer bootcamp activities held by the Kampus Merdeka and Ruang Guru.

Front-end Developer | Skill Academy By Ruang Guru - Yogyakarta, Indonesia Jun 2022 – Jul 2022

Creating a digital library website for the final project from Ruang Guru with the team as the Front End

Events Department | PORSEMATIF 2020 - HMIF Indonesian Islamic University Nov 2020 - Jan 2021

• Organize the event before, during, after the event

Events Department | Informatics Program for Unity within Ta'aruf - Indonesian Dec 2021 - Jan 2022

- Organize the event before, during, after the event
- Become a non-formal event host during the activity

Front-end Developer And Data Researcher | Kuliah Kerja Nyata Universitas Islam Indonesia - Indonesian Aug 2022 - Sep 2022

- Developing Bandungrejo Website
- Collecting data needed for village website development

PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Commitment
- Motivating
- Time Management
- Creative
- Interpersonal Skills
- Willingness to learn
- Teamwork Skills
- Flexibility